Guide to the Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, General Committee of the New York Central Railroad (Lines West), chairman's files, 1909-1962 [bulk 1931-1962].
Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, General Committee of the New York Central Railroad (Lines West), chairman's files, 1909-1962 [bulk 1931-1962].
- 3-4. Personal Papers, Receipts, and Correspondence.
  - Reports of General Chairmen (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Personal Letters (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Leave of Absence Forms (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Tax Returns (quarterly) 1936-37) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Railroad Retirement Beard (1935-51) Receipts, Certificate of Service (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - I.R.S./Railroad Retirement Board (1937 - 44). (Box 2, Folder 9)
- 3-5. Employee Benefits and Regulations.
  - By-laws (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - By-laws (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Social Security Act - 1936 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Benefits for Railroad Employees - pamphlets (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Diagrams of Provisions for Employees (Box 2, Folder 5)
- 3-6. Civil Improvements.
  - Agreements and Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Case of Race Motor Sales (Box 2, Folder 2)
- 4-1. Work Claims.
  - Shoemaker, Drum, Halbut (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Ragsdale (Box 3, Folder 2)
- 4-2. Inspector/Foreman Agreement, 1954-1956.
  - Lines West (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Lines East (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence (1952-54) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Rate Adjustment (1952-54) (Box 3, Folder 4)
- 4-3. Financial Agreements.
  - Signalman's Relief Fund (1931-32) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Union Pacific Railroad (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - South Pacific Railroad vs. Brotherhood of Railroad Signalman (1930) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Railway Labor Act (1926-29) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Aurand (direct correspondence) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Weigand (direct correspondence) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence between Aurand and Pattee (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Forty Hour Work Week Agreement (1949-50) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Political League (1954) (Box 3, Folder 9)
- 4-4. Inspector/Foreman Agreements, 1957-1961.
  - Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Multiple Copies of Agreement (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Revised Agreement (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Car Retarder Technicians (1957-60) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Pittsburgh Lake Erie Railroad Agreement (1953) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Changes in District 2 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- 5-1. Grand Lodge Headquarters.
  - Quarterly Financial Statements (1934-41) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Quarterly Financial Statements (1949-62) (Box 4, Folder 2)
- 5-3. Signal Department Seniority Rosters.
  - Northern District (1958-62) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Canada Division (1951-52, 1954-62) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Erie Signal District (1954-62 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Cleveland Signal District (1954-62 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Toledo Signal District (1954-60) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Western Signal District (1956-59; 1962 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Chicago Terminal Signal District (1954-62) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Southern District (1954-61) (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Cleveland Union Terminal (1954-60 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Indiana Harbor Belt Railway District (1949-61) (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Elkhart Signal Shop (1949-62 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Ohio Central District (1953-62 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Indiana Division (1954-62) (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Illinois Division (1954-62) (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Pittsburgh Lake Erie Railroad Co. (1951-59) (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Western District No. 2 - Inspector-Foreman (1953-61) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Southern District No. 3 - Foremen, Inspectors (1953-61 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Northern District No. 4 - (1956-63) (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Northern District No. 5 (1956-61) (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Retarder Technicians, District No. 7 (1962) (Box 4, Folder 20)
- 6-1. Officer's Reports.
  - Report of General Officers for Period 11/1/36-10/31/38 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Officer's Reports and Minutes of August 1952 Convention (Box 4, Folder 2)
- 6-2. Wages.
  Materials on wages (1926-1956) include discussion of railroad organizations cooperating in opposing the national wage reduction movement inaugurated by the carriers.
  - 1938 Controversy and Settlement (3/38) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Pamphlets on Railroad Wages (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 1932 Wage Reduction Proposal (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 1931 Wage Reduction Proposal (Box 4, Folder 4)
- 7-1. Wage Revisions.
  - 1926 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Wage Increase of 1929 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Agreement 4/1/29 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Wage Increase (1937) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Wage Increase (1941) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Wage Increase Request (1947) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Wage Increase Request (1948) (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Request for Increase (1950) (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - National Wage Actions (1949) (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - List of Rates (U.S. and Canada) 1947-56 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Wage Increase (1955) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - 1956 Wage Movement (Box 5, Folder 13)
- 7-2. Veteran's Benefits.
  Materials on veterans (1944-1949) include agreements and letters covering employees entering and leaving military service.
  - Vacations/Seniority Rights (1942-46) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Re-employment Rights (1940-46) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Merchant Marines (1947) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Employment Policy (1941 and 45) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Selective Training and Service Act (1940) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - On the Job Training (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Reenlistment (1947-48) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Promotions (1946-50) (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Vacation Cases (1946- ) (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Education Benefits (1946) (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Education Benefits - Leaves of Absence (1946- (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Seniority /Enlistment (1944-46) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Bureau of Veterans Re-employment Rights - Field Letters (1949-51) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Re-employment Rights Continued by Extension of Social Security Act (1950) (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Reinstatement Rights (1951-52) (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Leave of Absence for Enlistment (1951) (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Vacated Positions (1951-52) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Public Law 51 - Employees in Military Service (1951) (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Public Laws - Vocational Rehabilitation Publications (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Veteran's Readjustment Act 1952 Policy (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Displacement Rights (1956) (Box 5, Folder 21)
- 7-3. Consolidations/Absorptions.
  Materials on consolidation and absorptions (1932-1959) include a proposed rule governing adjustment of employee seniority affected by consolidation of seniority districts; letters regarding bidding rights, merger of and consolidation of seniority districts; a report, agreement, and letter regarding the protection of rights and interests of railway employees in any consolidation or unification of railroad facilities; seniority dispute between locals; seniority consolidation rule; displacement rights; and a membership drive by the American Railway Supervisors' Association of the New York Central system, conducted among signal inspectors and general foremen.
  - Agreement 12/20/34 revised 7/2/36 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Michigan Central (1931) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Erie and Franklin Divisions (1932) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Old Illinois Division (1932) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Grand Rapids (1934-36) Unification of Terminals (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Michigan Central/NYC (1934-35) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Michigan Central/Seniority Rights (1937-39) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Illinois Division/Seniority Districts (1947-50) (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Western Signal District-Seniority (1949-50) (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Agreement, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Seniority Dispute - Western Signal District/Chicago Terminal District (1932-35) (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - (Consolidated) Seniority Roster (1946) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Peoria and Eastern Railroad - Indianapolis (1934-35, 1944) (Box 5, Folder 13)
- 7-4. Centralized Traffic Control.
  - Pamphlets concerning CTC (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Memorandum - Positions connected with CTC Erie Division (1955-57) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Extension of CTC Installations (1955-57) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Western District Agreement, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Installation between Elkhart, Ind./ Jackson, Michigan (1957) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Employment under CTC/Yard Extension Program (1957) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Differential Pay Rates (1955-56) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Agreement - Seniority District - Ohio and Indiana Divisions, Change in Jurisdictions (1956-57) (Box 5, Folder 8)
- 7-5. Labor Relations, 1957-.
  - Position of Signal Maintainer (1957) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Operating Practices for Gateway Yard (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Maintenance Foreman (1957) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - New Agreement, Inspectors/Foremen (1957) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Educational and Training Program (1957) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - CTC "Territory" (1957) (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Lunch Time (1957) (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Highway Crossing Protection (1957 - 58) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Assistant Training Program (1957) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Lay-Offs/Unexcused Absence (1957) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - "Notice" (Section 6 -Railway Labor Act) (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Dispute Railway Employees Department / New York Central Railroad (1960). (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Furloughed Employee Status (1956-59) (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Railroad Retirement Board (1958-59) (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Working in the Rain (1958) (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Transfer of Signal Maintenance Sections From Western Signal District to Chicago Terminal District (1959) (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Pipe Work - Craft Jurisdiction (1958) (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Trench Work - Jurisdiction (1958) (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Seniority Status of J.C. Wyatt (1960-62) (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Signal Shop at Elkhart (1958) (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Canada: Highway Crossing Protective Devices (1957-59) (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Lost Time - Due to Medical Exam (1958-59) (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Canada Division-District 3 (1958) (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Accident at Ligonie, Ind. /Dismissals (1958) (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Signalman's Agreement - Labor Relations (1958) (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Seniority Case - Elkhart, Ind. (1958-61) (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Chauffeur's Licenses - N.Y.S. (1958-59) (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Maintenance Coverage, Erie CTC (1958) (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Name Change From BRS of A to BRS (1958-59) (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Consolidation of Locals 28 and 42 (1959) (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Passenger Train Service Bill (1960) (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Transfer of Local Jurisdiction (locals 15, 30, 41) (1959) (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Signal Construction Force (1959) (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Inspection Force (1959) (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - A.J. Scheider Case (1958-59) (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Increase Per Capita Tax to Grand Lodge (1959) (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Membership Transfer (Local 76 to 210) (1959) (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Status of two employees at High Bridge, N.Y., Signal Shop (1953-59) (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Investigation of Derailment at Short Cut Interlocker, 1959, Detroit, Toledo and Ironton Railroad Co. (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Repair of Electronic Equipment (1959) (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Case Wiring Work at Lyons, NY (1959) (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Hump Classification Yard at Indianapolis (1959) (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Reimbursement of Mr. Kalyncz (1959) (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Lunch Period - Cleveland Signal District (1959) (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Vacations (Erie Division) (1959) (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Michigan Cooperative Safety Plan (1959) (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Annual Vacation Act: Canada (1959) (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Transfer of Jurisdiction over Ohio Central Division from West to South District (7/59) (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - System Signal Shop Roster (1959) Displacement Routes at High Bridge, NY (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Representation of Signalmen - Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Co. (195 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Landrum-Griffith Act (1959) (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Ohio AFL-CIO (1959) (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Mediation Agreement (1959) (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Unexcused Absences - Elkhart Shop (1959) (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Company Policy of Father/Son Working Together (1959) (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Rearrangement in Western Operating District (1956-71) Diagrams (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Commutation Traffic Study (1955) New York City (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Vacation Agreement (1949) (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Affiliation/Constitution AFL-CIO (1956) (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - State Voting Procedures (Time Off) 1956 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Detroit Bomb Shelter Company (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - 1956 Wage Agreement (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Agreement of Louisville and Nashville Railroad Co. (1955) (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Grievances (Box 6, Folder 65)
- 8-1. Highways.
  - Highway Commission (1931-38) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Michigan State Projects (Highway) (Box 6, Folder 2)
- 8-2. Foremen.
  - Wage Compensation (1938-39) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Foremen - Promotions (1936-42) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - ICC Employee Classification/National Mediation Board (1941-47) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Case of A. A. Unmitz/W.K.Hunt (1940-41) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Office of Education (1942) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Expense Account (1939-41) (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Agreement-Governing Foreman Position (1921) (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Performing Work Belonging to Employees (1931-50) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Notice of Foreman Positions (1937-47) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Foremans Agreement (1924) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America Agreement (Representing Foremen and Inspectors in Dispute ) 1952 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Promotions and Representation of Foremen by BRS of A (1937-51) (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Advertise Positions Temporarily Vacant (1953) (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Proposed Revision to Foremen's Agreement (1953-54) (Box 6, Folder 14)
- 8-3. Vacations.
  Materials on vacation include (1931-1953) letters on vacation with pay, plan for vacation, vacation for non-operating employees, vacation allowance to estate of deceased employee, vacation for those entering military service, vacation schedule, vacation to employees on 3-trick assignments (1940-1951), and vacation agreements with drafts and revisions (1931-1953).
  - Vacation Pay (1940-42) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Vacations With Pay (1940-41) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Vacation Plan for 1943 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Vacation Plan for 1944 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Vacation Plan for 1945 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Vacation Plan for 1946 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Vacation Plan for 1947 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Vacation Plan for 1948 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Vacation Plan for 1949 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Vacation Plan for 1950, 1951, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Vacation Plan for 1953 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Decisions-Vacations for Non Operating Employees (1941) (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - NRAB-Dispute Claim (1950) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Claim of L.J. Kensler (1947-49) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Claim of T.A. Kilian (1944-45) (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Claim of Hoffman and Darby (1946) (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Claim of Gordon Jones (1947) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Claim of R.C. Hughes (1950) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Men at the W, Hump, Detroit (1949) (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Men Entering Military Service (1951) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Elkhart Indiana 1951 Vacation Schedule (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Toledo, Ohio - 1950 Memo (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Messrs. Langely and Clark (1951) (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Case of A. Lohrum (1953) (Box 7, Folder 24)
- 8-4. Agreements.
  - Agreement Between Indiana Harbor Belt. Co. BRSA (1951) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Agreement (1951) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Consolidated Agreement (1944-53) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - BRSA/NYC 1940 Agreement - Peoria and Eastern Railroad -Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis Railroad (1931-40) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Revision of Agreement (1935-40) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Proposed Revisions /Negotiations (1937-38) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Agreement 3/5/40 - Big Four/BRSA (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Revision of Michigan Central Agreement -Negotiations (1943) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 1950 Consolidated Agreement - Proposed Revisions (1947-50) (Box 7, Folder 10)
- 8-5. 40-Hour Work Week Agreements.
  - Indiana Harbor Belt Company /BRSofA 1949 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Big Four - 1949 Supplement (1950) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Indiana Harbor Belt Company 1949 Supplement and Revisions (1950) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Memorandum of Agreement Pittsburgh and Lake Erie (1950) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Supplement to Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Agreement (1950) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Committee Decisions (1949-50) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Force Reductions (1949) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Cleveland Local: Schedule Dispute (1949) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Deviation From Monday-Friday Work (1949) memo (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Lousiville and Nashville/Nashville, Chattanooga and St. Louis Memo Agreement 1949 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Pay Dispute (1949) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Claim of H.M. Thompson concerning Pay 1949 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Claim of G. Orndorff (1950) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Agreement 3/19/49 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- 8-6. Overtime.
  - Memo of Rule 18 Revision (1949) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Indiana Harbor Belt Co. Agreement Revision (1950) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Memo Revision (1949) (Box 8, Folder 3)
- 8-7. Canadian District.
  Materials on the Canadian District Public Relations include letters regarding Canadian members coming into the United States and exercising seniority rights (1941) and Canadian selective service order regarding government employment of union members to further the war effort (1942).
  - Seniority Rights in International District (1947) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Six Holidays (1942) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - General Orders - Railway Commissioners of Canada (1935) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Income Tax Deduction (1947) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Selective Service Data (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Wage Standards (1941-46) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Orders in Council (9/41) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - General Order (5/51) (Box 8, Folder 8)
- 8-8. Public Relations.
  - Pamphlets/Information (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Labor-Management Relations (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Railway Labor Relations (1948) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Personnel (1951) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Contribution of Employees to Good Public Relations (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Definition of a Customer (1952) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Pension Rackets (Box 8, Folder 7)
- 9-1. Consolidation.
  - Federal Employer's Liability Act (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Representation of Signal Draftsmen (1953) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Installation of Nuclear Switch Lamps (1954-60) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - ICC - Employee Classification (1953) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Revision of Basic Agreements (1957) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Transfer of Maintenance Section (1954) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Application to National Mediation Board (1954) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Working On/Near Highway Crossings (1954-56) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Recall of Furloughed Employees on Michigan Central (1955) (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Submission of Claims-Grievances (1955) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Meeting March 21, 1955 re 1954 Agreement (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Lakefront Dock and Railroad Terminal Co. (1955) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Leaves of Absence to Permit Employees to Engage in Outside Employment (1$ (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Indiana Gross Income Tax (1954-57) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Cooperating Railway Labor Organizations (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Housing Units for Signal Gongs (1955) (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Jury Duty (Absence for) (1955-61) (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Canadian National Railway - Signal Maintenance (1956) (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Equipment Budget (1955-) (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Position Numbers (1955-53) (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - 10 - A or Surprise Test (1950-52). (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Railway Labor Act (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Railroad Transportation Act (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Association of American Railroads (1958) (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Rules and Regulations Governing Railroad Radio Service (1945) (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - System Signal Shop (1954-61) (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Maintenance of Rail Head Bonds (1951-52) (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Signal Department Questionnaire (1952) (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - New York Central Railroad - Personnel Information (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Detroit Terminal Railroad (1952-61) (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - American Railway Supervisors Association (1953) (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Investigations and Hearings (1947-52) (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Car Retarders (1949-53) (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Overtime and Seniority (1955-56) (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Signal Inspection Test (1956) (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Supervisory Forces Hauling Signal Material (1956) (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Installation of Snow Melters on Erie Division (1957-61) (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Case of J. Pempeck (1951-56) (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - South District-Installation and Procurement of Factory Wired Relay Cases and Housings (1957) (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - By-Laws Governing General System Committee (Box 8, Folder 4l)
  - State Public Service Acts Pertaining to Railroads (1949-57) (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Operation of Company Trucks (1958-61) (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Double-Time Rate After 15 Hours (1952-53) (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - "60 Calendar Days" Revision (1960-62) (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Responsibilities of Leading Signal Mechanic (1952) (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - 30 Minute Lunch Period (1951-52) (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Pay Claim of L.J. Miller (1951-52) (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Pay for Temporary Position (1952) (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Claim for Expenses for Meal Period Under Rule 18 (1954) (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Displacement Routes (1952-53) (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Strike Settlement Claims (1952-54) (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Promoted Man's Position Abolished (1952) (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Promotions (1952) (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Case of Toronto, Hamilton, and Buffalo (1955) (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Travel Time (1952-53) (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Furnish Soap for Cars (1952) (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Rates of Pay for Leading Signal Maintenances (1952-53) (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Heating Facilities (1951 - 1954). (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Seniority/Higher Pay Rates (1952/61) (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Overtime Claim of D.J. Britton (1954-56) (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Application of Rule 33 (1955) (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Make-Up Time (Rule 18) (1958-59) (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Overtime - D.L. Shultz (1959) (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Telephone at Company Expense (1946-53) (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Filing of Claims (1958) (Box 8, Folder 66)
- 11-1. Miscellaneous.
  - Plant Transportation Committee (1942-44) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - District Construction Gangs (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Special Board of Adjustment (1960) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Elkhart Signal Shop Consolidation (1954-55) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Vacation and Holiday Rules Movement (1959) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Health and Welfare, Life Insurance, Cost-of-Living Escalator (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 1961 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Expense Sheets (1954-58) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Meeting of Executive Committee and Signal Engineers in Detroit (1954 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Agreement NYC/Retarder Technicians, Inspectors Foremen Employed in Signal Department (1958-60) (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Tax Statements (1960-61) (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Bound Ledger of Personal Expenses (1952-58) (Box 9, Folder 13)
- 13. Work Claims and Disputes.